{"sid": "KU8TMJGIXF3A_main", "calc_equals_delay": 3, "block_data": {"block_0": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 425979, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "300", "question_time_start": 425980, "question": "3+44+28", "correct_answer": 75, "events": [["calc_7", 443364], ["calc_+", 444801], ["calc_2", 445736], ["calc_8", 446573], ["calc_=", 447564], ["submit", 462239]], "used_calculator": "True", "time_left_end": "264", "answered_time": 462239, "user_answer": "75", "user_correct": "True", "score": "1"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "264", "question_time_start": 462239, "question": "4+3+8+98", "correct_answer": 113, "events": [["submit", 478277]], "time_left_end": "248", "answered_time": 478277, "user_answer": "113", "user_correct": "True", "score": "2"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "248", "question_time_start": 478277, "question": "3+7+4+24", "correct_answer": 38, "events": [["submit", 483144]], "time_left_end": "243", "answered_time": 483144, "user_answer": "38", "user_correct": "True", "score": "3"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "243", "question_time_start": 483144, "question": "3+79+88", "correct_answer": 170, "events": [["submit", 496467]], "time_left_end": "230", "answered_time": 496467, "user_answer": "170", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "230", "question_time_start": 496468, "question": "7+3+7+68", "correct_answer": 85, "events": [["submit", 509184]], "time_left_end": "217", "answered_time": 509184, "user_answer": "95", "user_correct": "False", "score": "3"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "217", "question_time_start": 509184, "question": "9+3+13", "correct_answer": 25, "events": [["submit", 513898]], "time_left_end": "213", "answered_time": 513898, "user_answer": "25", "user_correct": "True", "score": "4"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "213", "question_time_start": 513899, "question": "23+37", "correct_answer": 60, "events": [["submit", 518032]], "time_left_end": "208", "answered_time": 518032, "user_answer": "60", "user_correct": "True", "score": "5"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "208", "question_time_start": 518032, "question": "76+47", "correct_answer": 123, "events": [["submit", 544341]], "time_left_end": "182", "answered_time": 544341, "user_answer": "123", "user_correct": "True", "score": "6"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "182", "question_time_start": 544341, "question": "16+786", "correct_answer": 802, "events": [["submit", 552033]], "time_left_end": "174", "answered_time": 552033, "user_answer": "802", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "174", "question_time_start": 552033, "question": "9+4+68", "correct_answer": 81, "events": [["submit", 557561]], "time_left_end": "169", "answered_time": 557561, "user_answer": "79", "user_correct": "False", "score": "6"}}}, "block_1": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 557561, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "169", "question_time_start": 557561, "question": "16+867", "correct_answer": 883, "events": [["submit", 566887]], "time_left_end": "160", "answered_time": 566887, "user_answer": "883", "user_correct": "True", "score": "7"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "160", "question_time_start": 566887, "question": "29+37", "correct_answer": 66, "events": [["submit", 575903]], "time_left_end": "151", "answered_time": 575903, "user_answer": "66", "user_correct": "True", "score": "8"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "151", "question_time_start": 575903, "question": "6+39+49", "correct_answer": 94, "events": [["submit", 587769]], "time_left_end": "139", "answered_time": 587769, "user_answer": "94", "user_correct": "True", "score": "9"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "139", "question_time_start": 587769, "question": "56+47", "correct_answer": 103, "events": [["submit", 595122]], "time_left_end": "131", "answered_time": 595122, "user_answer": "103", "user_correct": "True", "score": "10"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "131", "question_time_start": 595122, "question": "8+7+3+23", "correct_answer": 41, "events": [["submit", 621695]], "time_left_end": "105", "answered_time": 621695, "user_answer": "41", "user_correct": "True", "score": "11"}, "q5": {"time_left_start": "105", "question_time_start": 621695, "question": "4+8+9+76", "correct_answer": 97, "events": [["submit", 639852]], "time_left_end": "87", "answered_time": 639852, "user_answer": "97", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q6": {"time_left_start": "87", "question_time_start": 639852, "question": "4+29+87", "correct_answer": 120, "events": [["submit", 650962]], "time_left_end": "76", "answered_time": 650962, "user_answer": "110", "user_correct": "False", "score": "11"}, "q7": {"time_left_start": "76", "question_time_start": 650963, "question": "4+8+16", "correct_answer": 28, "events": [["submit", 655623]], "time_left_end": "71", "answered_time": 655623, "user_answer": "28", "user_correct": "True", "score": "12"}, "q8": {"time_left_start": "71", "question_time_start": 655623, "question": "7+9+7+88", "correct_answer": 111, "events": [["submit", 670109]], "time_left_end": "56", "answered_time": 670109, "user_answer": "111", "user_correct": "True", "score": "13"}, "q9": {"time_left_start": "56", "question_time_start": 670110, "question": "7+9+49", "correct_answer": 65, "events": [["submit", 680806]], "time_left_end": "46", "answered_time": 680806, "user_answer": "65", "user_correct": "True", "score": "14"}}}, "block_2": {"mean_level": 7, "start_time": 680806, "questions": {"q0": {"time_left_start": "46", "question_time_start": 680806, "question": "8+34+13", "correct_answer": 55, "events": [["submit", 691499]], "time_left_end": "35", "answered_time": 691499, "user_answer": "55", "user_correct": "True", "score": "15"}, "q1": {"time_left_start": "35", "question_time_start": 691499, "question": "47+43", "correct_answer": 90, "events": [["submit", 696115]], "time_left_end": "30", "answered_time": 696115, "user_answer": "90", "user_correct": "True", "score": "16"}, "q2": {"time_left_start": "30", "question_time_start": 696115, "question": "9+8+9+93", "correct_answer": 119, "events": [["submit", 709086]], "time_left_end": "17", "answered_time": 709086, "user_answer": "119", "user_correct": "True", "score": "17"}, "q3": {"time_left_start": "17", "question_time_start": 709087, "question": "93+773", "correct_answer": 866, "events": [["submit", 723258]], "time_left_end": "3", "answered_time": 723258, "user_answer": "866", "user_correct": "True", "score": "18"}, "q4": {"time_left_start": "3", "question_time_start": 723258, "question": "9+7+3+97", "correct_answer": 116, "events": []}}}}}